William Lin

US Citizen Email: wlin6680@protonmail.ch 13293B Kalmia Ln Apt 203 Fairfax, VA 22033 Phone: (202) 386-8943

Objective:

A motivated and fast learning IT Support Technician, who is keen on applying academic foundation and practical training in the field. Experienced in software and operating system installations and troubleshooting issues as they arise. Experience working as a sales advisor and have polished client relation skills and be able to provide exceptional customer service support in a technical and diverse settings. Past experiences with web development could be leveraged to build a website to monitor system deployment and installation statuses.

Skills:

Software Proficiency: Microsoft Office Suite, Notepad++, jGrasp, Atom,VMWare, **Operating Systems**: Windows XP, 7, 8, 10, Mac OSX, Window Server 2012 and

2016

Certifications: A+ Certification
Web Development: CSS, HTML
Languages: English, Chinese

Work Experience:

Logistic and Repair Technician | TelosID | February 2019 - Present | Full-Time

- Ensure compliance with established internal control procedures and creation of new procedure when needed
- Maintain inventory levels for standard installation materials while coordinating with field staff to determine parts requirements
- Point of Contact for other members of the Tier III DMDC Support team for hardware related issue, and providing technical assistance to system end users.
- Responsible for reading the detailed prescription sheets sent in by laboratories.
- Configuring replacement system based on end user requirement

Dental Lab Technician | Protech Dental Studio | November 2017 - February 2019 | Full-Time

- Scan physical dental models into database to be digitally designed
- Using digital scan of patient teeths to create 3D models
- Collaborate with Carbon3D to printed resin teeth models
- Collaborate with dental vendor's representative to ensure proper quality control
- Responsible for reading the detailed prescription sheets sent in by laboratories.

IT Support Technician | Protech Dental Studio | March 2018 - February 2019 | Full-Time

- Installed, configured, and maintained PC workstation operations
- Created, solved, escalated, and documented tickets through CWPS

- Created monthly backup of patient information
- Managed and tracked computer assets such as desktops, laptops, monitors, and various printers located throughout the office
- Collaborate with CWPS to maintain office workstations
- Create and maintain company-based windows image for deployment

Sales Advisor | Club Demonstration Services | November 2012-December 2017 | Part-Time

- Demonstration of food and non-food vendor products to members.
- Influence sale of vendor products.
- Customer Interaction with vendor products.
- Response to customer questions and request in a prompt and efficient manner
- Prepare organized work environment for other Advisor to speed up work preparations

Education:

George Mason University

Fairfax, Virginia

Pursuing Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology with Minor in Business

Coursework:

- IT Problem Solving
- Introductory Calculus with Business Applications

Present

Northern Virginia Community College

Annandale, Virginia

Associate Degree in Information Technology

Coursework:

- Advanced Database Management
- PC Hardware & O/S Architecture
- JAVA Programming, I
- Introduction to Telecommunications

Finished in May 2016